A Guide to the New River Community College. Office of the President. Correspondence and subject files, 1969-1981
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
New River Community College. Office of the President. Correspondence and subject files, 1969-1981
The Library of Virginia
31390, 31271, 32678
50 cu. ft. (50 boxes)
New River Community College. Office of the President.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 24 June 1981 from the New River Community College, Dublin, Virginia 24084 [Accession 31271].
Transferred on 20 April 1982 from the New River Community College, Dublin, Virginia 24084 [Accession 31390].
Transferred on 28 February 1986 from the New River Community College, Dublin, Virginia 24084 [Accession 32678].
Biographical Information
Scope and Content
These records consist of the correspondence and subject files of the community college president. May include incoming and outgoing correspondence, memoranda and reports that document the functions, activities and policies of the office and the community college.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1970-1977 [Accession 31271]
Series II: Correspondence and subject files, 1977-1979 [Accession 31390]
Series I: Correspondence and subject files, 1979-1981 [Accession 32678]
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31271], 1970-1977., Extent: cu. ft. (boxes) (Box 1)
  - AAS Degree programs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Academic honors, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Academic Freedom Act, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Academic instruction, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Academic program, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Acceptances, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Accounting system, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Activities calendar, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Adjunct faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Admission requirements, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Admission of students with high school equivalent, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Administrators, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Adult drivers education, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Advertising, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Academic and student affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council to the President, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Agricultural education, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Agronomy, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Air conditioning, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Air travel, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Alcoholism counselors, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol safety action program, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Allied Chemical Corp., 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Association for Community and Junior Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Vocational Association, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - American Waterworks Association, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Appalachian Awareness Week, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Appalachian Regional, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Appendix M, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Application files, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Applications for graduation, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Application letters, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Appropriation reduction, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Appointment proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship programs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Aptitude ability tests, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Area X Manpower Planning Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Architects, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Army, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Arts America program, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Crafts Center, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Articulation, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Artmobile Collegiate programs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Association of Community Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Attendance policy, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Auditing, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Audit students, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Audiovisual department, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Author for out of state travel, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Automotive programs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Banking and financial programs, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Balls and Crillons, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Bland Correctional Center, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Blood mobile, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Bluefield State College, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Bluefield Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Bond issues, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Book store, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Bureaucratic conflict, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Business in arts, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Business and public services technologies, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Busing of students, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Capital outlay, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Carboning of letters, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Career day, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Car rental, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Catalogs, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Categories of employees, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Certified public accountant examination, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Certified professional secretary credit, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Change orders, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Chart of accounts, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Cheating policy, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Child care program, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Choral festival, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Circle K, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Classroom reservations, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Class rosters, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Class status report, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Classroom positions, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Collection of delinquent accounts, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Agenda, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Floyd County, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Giles County, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Montgomery County, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Pulaski County, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Radford City, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Invoices, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Office, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, Members, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Board, News, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College calendar, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College catalog, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College day, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College law conference, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College level examinations, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College service area, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - College Standing Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Commendation letters, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Common residency forms, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Common college frontiers, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Common college review, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Community education, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Community obligations, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Community services, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Community and social services program, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Committee on committees, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Compensation, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Computer, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Conference calls, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Conflict of interest, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Construction of facilities, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Continuing education, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Contractual agreements, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Cooperative education, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Copies, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Corning glass works, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Coronary care program, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Counseling, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Count Pulaski Day, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Course loads, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Course objectives, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Course plans, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Course revisions, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Credit cards, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Cultural exchange programs, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Criminal justice program, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dalton Theater, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Danville Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Data processing, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Deaf students, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Financial and Administrative Services, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Instructions Council, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Students Services Council, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Defense driving program, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Corrections, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Desegregation of state systems, Public Higher education, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Development courses, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Developmental studies, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dictation equipment, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Directory of Administrative Officers, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dismissal of college personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dissertations, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Discriminations, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Division chairman, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Division of Business and Public Service Technologies, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Division of Mathematics, Science, and Nursing Technologies, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Division of Humanities and Social Services, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Doctoral programs, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Dos and Don't for new presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Duplicating, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Drug education program, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Drama, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Drafting and design program, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Early learning center, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Economics of regulations, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational aid requests, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational master plan, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational programs, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational records, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Electricity, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Election day, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational testing service, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Electrical conditions, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Emergency services, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Employees, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Employment plan, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Energy conservation, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Engineering and industrial technologies division, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - English department, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Enrollment, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Environmental control operators, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Equal opportunity, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Equipment, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Established salaried positions, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Evening duty, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Exams, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Facilities, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Family directory, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Family educational rights and privacy act, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - FBI Academy, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Federal grants, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Federal legislation, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Federal Mogul, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Federal register, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Federal reorganization, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Federal research report, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Financial aid, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Financial consultants, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Financial management programs, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Financial statements, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Fire safety, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Flood disaster in SW Virginia, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Floyd County High School, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Follow up of graduates, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Food services, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Foreign language, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Forensic science program, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Free enterprise, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Fringe benefits, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - General Assembly, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Giles County High School, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Gifts, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Goals, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Governors capital outlay budget, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Governors manpower planning, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grade analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grade appeal, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grade inflation, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grade study report, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grades, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Graduate assistantships, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Graduates, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grievance procedures, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Grounds, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Group discussion, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Handicapped, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Health, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - HEW fellowships, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Hercules, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Higher education, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Highway safety, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box \5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - , 1976-1977 (Box 5)